Hi! Welcome to this video. Today is all about black leggings. I'm going to
declutter all my black faux leather, wet look, shiny whatever leggings. So stay
with me, it's going to be really messy and I'll show you my favorites. This is
it all black leggings here and it's such a mess I'm going to do this all right
let's get started I'm just going to delve into it and pick the first one
that is on top oh yeah a slinky styles leggings I think this is actually this
is my newest leggings. I just took some pictures with it. I'm going to show you.
And it's, I like to call it the looks like panties over the leggings type.
This is pretty cool. It fits really good. Oh my god, I'm going to say this sentence
like 100 times today. I don't know. Anyway, I am definitely going to keep this one
because it's really comfortable and it's brand new and I'm going to have to wear it. All right.
Oh yeah, this one is nice. So this is a, I would call it matte PVC leggings by Patrice Catanzaro.
I do have a catsuit similar to the leggings in terms of materials. So same
material but catsuit. Let's have a look here at the picture. And there's also a
jumpsuit up review with the catsuit. I'm going to link it. And this leggings is so
comfortable and it is so cool. I'm going to wear it now. This video is going to be
so messy and a bit trashy, I hope you don't mind it. This is another Slinky
Styles. To be honest I do not remember the names of all of these because they're a
weird combination of letters and numbers.
I only know that this one makes a really great boutique.
And yeah, there are going to be a lot of Slinky Styles leggings because I have
cooperation with them.
I'm doing a lot of pictures for them and in return I can keep the leggings.
But no, I'm not earning money. I just like to wear leggings, so
that's cool. Definitely going
to keep these as well. Maybe I should do a Slinky Styles pile and a other brand's pile. I don't know yet.
Something shiny. Oh yeah, these are my Paradise pants, PVC version. I recently did a video with them.
and I love their cut. So comfortable. I'm definitely going to keep them and keep wearing them because they're super cool.
And somewhere here has to be the leather version.
I think this is one yeah so this is the second paradise pants I own with the
black zipper and I think these are like the best-fitting leggings I own I mean
of course the other ones are good as well but there are some differences next what's that oh
yeah this is a slinky styles one I think it is actually like the same than the last one
but slightly different material so a bit more shiny and less shiny but it's basically the
same cut, the same leggings and they do make a great booty as well. These are like my two
favorite basic Slinky Styles leggings. Let's see what we can find from Slinky Styles. For
example this one. It's a classic PVC leggings with a crotch zipper which is really really
cool when you want to go to the toilet but you're wearing a corset and the leggings underneath
so that was a wish of mine to receive leggings like that they're super shiny but the thing is
it's really not that stretchy when it comes to the waist here and i have a really really hard time
getting into these so they're not my favorite leggings to wear I kind of
worried wearing them because it's so hard to get into. I don't mind going to keep them anyway
because they're great basic PVC leggings
Alright, what's next?
Oh yeah, another Slinky Styles leggings.
This is some kind of cool holographic PVC.
This has a roller beezle at the back again and I'm going to change into them now.
these are my trusty trusty fall leather leggings fun story about these leggings
I found them like two and a half years ago at the H&M in Brisbane Australia
when I spent some months there and yeah I've worn them ever since these leggings
are part of a lot of pictures a lot of videos and all the time people keep
asking me oh where are these leggings from and I'm like Australia Brisbane H&M
I doubt you'll find them now in Germany or wherever you are but yeah so two and a
half year old four leather leggings I've worn them so often they're still in
great condition I'm definitely going to keep them although I have to admit that
the Slinky Styles and Paradise Leggings do make a better body shape. Alright.
Oh yeah, next Slinky Styles Leggings. I have to count them I guess in the end.
This material is called Rubber Touch. Oh, there's no light. It's a really really
soft material and kind of, yeah, matte. Also shiny, I don't know. This is weird.
I'm going to keep these ones because the material is so smooth and so unique and I like to
wear them. So this one comes on top of the slinky styles pile. It's already the
biggest one. Just think. What's that? Oh okay I know. These are some winter
leggings so they have fleece on the inside so they're pretty pretty smugly
and soft and I think these are like from Amazon or something point is they're way
too short so I'm definitely going to get rid of them for once and for all because
I kind of tend to keep them now. I think these are like the same category. I'm
always looking for some good winter leggings with a good fit but as with the
ones before these are also way too short even shorter than the other ones anyway
it's not that I do not have any other leggings. Because I have a lot of leggings! Oh my gosh!
I could let like 40 more in the air and yeah. Next slinky style leggings. This was a
anti-countering leggings because to be honest like real talk now most of the
slinky styles leggings do make a rather big camel toe and I do not like camel toes I do not know
any other girls who like that I've heard of some people who like it but I've never met someone in
person so I asked slinky styles if they could do some anti-contouring leggings and this is one of
them. The first one I showed you has also an anti-contouring but it's a whole
different cut so never mind. This is the anti-contouring leggings. It's super cool
and super comfortable so I'm going to change into these. There are leggings on top of me.
There are leggings everywhere! Nevermind!
Yeah, some classic four leather leggings.
Oh yeah, wanted to put these ones aside.
It's not that bad, I thought it would be way worse.
Alright, I know this one.
This one is by Buzz Blue.
I think I have a second one from Buzz Blue.
Oh yeah, this is the one.
I really like them because they have a cool design.
They're not just some plain black leggings but they have like structured stuff going
on and some zippers, crisscross thingies, no idea. Did you know that Slinky Styles has a
second label which is called Sleek Cheek and Sleek Cheek is all about the soft materials
like spandex or this shimmery material, I don't even know what's it called, but it's really
shimmery and these are like the most comfortable leggings a bit see-through i bought them at the
Fernando Berlin showroom you can check that video out and i think there are pictures with them as well
of course there are so these are like so comfortable you can lay on the couch with them
not the best figure shaping ones obviously but never mind some days it's just about being comfy
oh it's getting getting less crowded down here cotton leggings yes i own cotton leggings
well these ones have some fake leather details sorry not sorry and they're from
Kelly Rose, a Swedish designer I like very much.
And these leggings are just adorable with the four letter applications and like snake skin-ish stuff.
I do own cordu-leggings, that's the proof.
Oh, some white look leggings from Punkrave.
they have kind of see-through slits here in the front. I did my very first styling videos and
pictures with them. Yeah, we always say. Keeping them. I still have to figure out how I'm going to
stack them on top of each other, because... Oh, there's another Pankray blingons. One I got only
recently but I did some dressing videos with this one and some pictures which
you can see here this was really cool with all the tiny belts going on here
and wet look as well so Pugrave pile
What's that?
Oh, it's another Slinky Styles leggings.
Who would have guessed?
This is a special fabric Slinky Styles leggings.
It's super cool. When I'm wearing it, it looks almost like jeans.
And it's the well-known Slinky Styles cup with the ball beater here.
I have no idea why I put this in a bag to be honest I'm going to put this back
in a bag because why not something colorful oh it's not only black leggings
now there are two colored leggings here
It is from Peter Domini, a Dutch designer.
There's a store in Berlin and these are super cool.
I'm going to change into them.
Yay, they're blue!
Just some kind of coated spandex, so they're a bit shiny.
The other ones from Peter Domini I own are these silver ones.
Oh the tags are still on.
I think I've never worn this one.
Shame on me.
I just got too many of them.
I did take some pictures with them.
I do remember now.
So I worn them in the hope that I'm going to wear them more often.
I'm going to keep them here together with the blue ones.
These are, what's this?
Pussy Riot leggings.
They are like plain black for the but
they have a zipper in the front and there's a cool
yeah triangle shape cut going on in front and in the back.
These are super comfortable.
they don't make any camel toe so they're going to stay
of course and my second pussy ride leggings are some of my favorite leggings
because the material is so cool it's kind of like really soft pvc and it's patterned there are some
rose patterns. It looks like there is floral lace over the leggings but it's just the leggings
itself. I like them so much. Two leggings out so far. I'm not really good at this. Can't believe
this but this is the last leggings I haven't showed you yet. It's confusing me for one.
And it is a Killstar leggings. Some kind of wet look or I don't know. Kind of reminds me of the Robo
church so he starts but this one has zippers at the knee and there is a
harness right at the crotch going on it's pretty cool I have to wear them I
did not wear them yet because I ordered them and I really liked them but then all
the festivals got cancelled all the parties got cancelled and you know how
it is. No occasion to wear them. Except now.
Hello! Alright, I like these ones really much. They're cool, they're comfortable. I know
I know I said this about all my leggings, but to be honest, if a leggings is not cool and not comfortable, it's not going to make it into my closet here.
I'm going to tell you a secret. There are leggings at other places as well.
Like, for example, here.
Or in the basement. I know that there is a whole box of sleep chic leggings in the basement.
so there are other leggings everywhere but this is like my primary leggings cupboard here so let's
put them on together. We have 1, 2, 3, 4, 14, 15 leggings from various brands and on
top of that. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight slinky style leggings. That makes
23 leggings in total. Yeah, 23. Is it though? Just kidding. And I'm going to put these up again
in the cupboard. Now at least they look nice again and they're folded and whatever.
Definitely have way too many leggings. Let's put them up here.
Oh and I forgot that I'm wearing a pair of leggings right now, so it's 16. And I put them in here.
it still looks kind of messy but at least they're folded and it only looks messy because of the
belts from the punk rave leggings so yeah thanks for sticking with me thanks for keeping me company
when i was decluttering my leggings i hope you had at least a bit of fun and
you don't think that I'm mad for owning so many leggings.
Sorry, not sorry. I really like leggings. But yeah, see you around. Bye.